Inventory of the Mills E. Godwin Jr. Papers 1947-1989
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Speeches, 1957-1978. (Box 17-24)
  - Speeches, 1967., 109 items. (Box 17-18)
    - Launching of Personna Hospital Charity Program, Staunton, Virginia, King's Daughters' Hospital, 11 January 1967. (Box 17)
    - Winchester chamber of Commerce, 12 January 1967. (Box 17)
    - Richmond Chamber of Commerce, Hotel John Marshall, 19 January 1967. (Box 17)
    - Governor's Regional Conference on Education, Mary Washington College, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 2 February 1967. (Box 17)
    - Norfolk General Hospital, Dedication of New Wing, 17 February 1967. (Box 17)
    - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, Hotel John Marshall, 18 February 1967. (Box 17)
    - Governor's Regional Conference on Education, Municipal Auditorium, Norfolk, Virginia, 23 February 1967. (Box 17)
    - Governor's Regional Conference on Education, Longwood College, Farmville, Virginia, 27 February 1967. (Box 17)
    - Governor's Regional Conference on Education, Roanoke, Virginia, 27 February 1967. (Box 17)
    - Bristol Regional Conference on Education, Virginia Junior High School Auditorium, Bristol, Virginia, 28 February 1967. (Box 17)
    - Governor's Regional Conference on Education, Madison College, Harrisonburg, Virginia, 3 March 1967. (Box 17)
    - Governor's Regional Conference on Education, Thomas Jefferson High School, Richmond, Virginia, 4 March 1967. (Box 17)
    - Southern Safety Conference Annual Meeting, John Marshall Hotel, 6 March 1967. (Box 17)
    - Emergency Planning Conference, State Capitol, Richmond, Virginia, 7 March 1967. (Box 17)
    - Governor's Regional Conference on Education, T. C. Williams High School, Alexandria, Virginia, 8 March 1967. (Box 17)
    - Randolph-Macon Woman's College, Nationwide Telephone Conference call, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 9 March 1967. (Box 17)
    - American Chamber of Commerce, Madrid, Spain, 31 March 1967. (Box 17)
    - Barcelona Chamber of Commerce, 3 April 1967. (Box 17)
    - American Chamber of Commerce, Turin, Italy, 5 April 1967. (Box 17)
    - American Chamber of Commerce, Milan, Italy, 6 April 1967. (Box 17)
    - American Club of Sweden, Stockholm, Sweden, 11 April 1967. (Box 17)
    - Association Belgo-Americaine, American Club of Brussels, Brussels, Belgium, 13 April 1967. (Box 17)
    - American Chamber of Commerce and American Belgium Association, Brussels, Belgium, 14 April 1967. (Box 17)
    - General Electric Plant Announcement, Governor's Office, 20 April 1967. (Box 17)
    - Dedication of Benjamin Harrison Memorial Bridge, Jordan Point, Virginia, 22 April 1967. (Box 17)
    - Dedication Ceremonies, Electra Motors, Inc., Ashland, Virginia, 26 April 1967. (Box 17)
    - State Agency Head Luncheon, Hotel John Marshall, 1 May 1967. (Box 17)
    - Seventy Millionth Ford Celebration, Golden Triangle Hotel, Norfolk, Virginia, 3 May 1967. (Box 17)
    - Presentation of "E" Award to Coulbourn Lumber Company, 4 May 1967. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Safety Association Thirty-Third Annual Safety Conference, Golden Triangle, Norfolk, Virginia, 11 May 1967. (Box 17)
    - Second Governors' Conference on Delmarva Development Convention Hall, Rehoboth Beach, Delaware, 11 May 1967. (Box 17)
    - Harold E. Watson Student Activities Building Dedication, Woodrow Wilson Rehabilitation Center, Staunton, Virginia, 17 May 1967. (Box 17)
    - Stackpole Components Company Plant Dedication, Farmville, Virginia, 21 May 1967. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Retail Merchants Association, Midtown Motor Hotel, Danville, Virginia, 21 May 1967. (Box 17)
    - Prelude to Independence, Williamsburg, Virginia, 27 May 1967. (Box 17)
    - Dedication of Scotchtown, Hanover County, Virginia, 28 May 1967. (Box 17)
    - Averett College, Danville, Virginia, 4 June 1967. (Box 17)
    - Rufus L. Patterson Tobacco Center Opening, Chesterfield County, Virginia, 5 June 1967. (Box 17)
    - Dedication, James River Sewage Treatment Plant, Hampton Roads Sanitation District Commission, Newport News, Virginia, 7 June 1967. (Box 17)
    - Churchland High School Commencement, 7 June 1967. (Box 17)
    - Memorial Dedication of the Harry F. Byrd, Sr. Visitor Center, Shenandoah National Park, 10 June 1967. (Box 17)
    - Western Virginia Community College Graduation, 10 June 1967. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute Commencement, Blacksburg, Virginia, 11 June 1967. (Box 17)
    - Roanoke Valley Council of Community Services Luncheon, 12 June 1967. (Box 17)
    - William Campbell High School Graduation, Brookneal, Virginia, 12 June 1967. (Box 17)
    - Chatham-Pittsylvania County Bicentennial Banquet, 15 June 1967. (Box 17)
    - Governor's Dinner, Charleston, South Carolina, 23 June 1967. (Box 17)
    - International Association of Personnel in Employment Security, John Marshall Hotel, 27 June 1967. (Box 17)
    - Dedication of Culpeper Wayside, 28 June 1967. (Box 17)
    - Technical Materials Plant Dedication, Alexandria, Virginia, 29 June 1967. (Box 17)
    - Formal Opening, Tavern Square, Alexandria, Virginia, 29 June 1967. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Foundation for Independent Colleges, The Homestead, Hot Springs, Virginia, 2 July 1967. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Automotive Trade Association, The Homestead, Hot Springs, Virginia, 9 July 1967. (Box 17)
    - Southern Regional Conference of Attorneys General, Williamsburg, Virginia, 10 July 1967. (Box 17)
    - Wallace Business Forms Plant Dedication, Luray, Virginia, 18 July 1967. (Box 17)
    - Old Dominion College, Norfolk, Virginia, 20 July 1967. (Box 17)
    - Motion Picture Association Convention, Virginia Beach, Virginia, 20 July 1967. (Box 17)
    - Wythe County Chamber of Commerce, 25 July 1967. (Box 17)
    - Big Walker Mountain Tunnel, 25 July 1967. (Box 17)
    - Democratic Campaign Kick-Off Dinner, Young Democratic Clubs of Virginia, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 9 September 1967. (Box 18)
    - Nuclear Energy and Space Committee Session, Southern Governors' Conference, Asheville, North Carolina, 11 September 1967. (Box 18)
    - Thomas Jefferson Award Dinner, Old Dominion Chapter, Public Relations Society of America, Hotel John Marshall, 15 September 1967. (Box 18)
    - Annual Convention, Virginia Municipal League, Golden Triangle, Norfolk, Virginia, 17 September 1967. (Box 18)
    - Half-time Ceremonies, VPI-W & M Football Game, Blacksburg, Virginia, 23 September 1967. (Box 18)
    - Smyth County Community Hospital, Marion, Virginia, 24 September 1967. (Box 18)
    - Introduction of William Thomas Rice, Hotel John Marshall, 27 September 1967. (Box 18)
    - Safety Awards Luncheon, Holiday Inn West, Richmond, Virginia, 28 September 1967. (Box 18)
    - Opening Tyson's Corner Center, Fairfax County, Virginia, 29 September 1967. (Box 18)
    - Northern Virginia Kick-Off Dinner, Arlington, Virginia, 29 September 1967. (Box 18)
    - 275th Anniversary of Richmond County, Warsaw, Virginia "Mt. Airy", 30 September 1967. (Box 18)
    - John Tyler Community College Dedication, Chester, Virginia, 4 October 1967. (Box 18)
    - Virginia School Boards Association, John Marshall Hotel, Richmond, Virginia, 5 October 1967. (Box 18)
    - Montgomery County Democratic Fund-Raising Dinner, Christiansburg, Virginia, 7 October 1967. (Box 18)
    - Salem Civic Center Dedication, Salem, Virginia, 8 October 1967. (Box 18)
    - General Electric Luncheon, 10 October 1967. (Box 18)
    - Virginia Probation and Parole Board, Twenty-fifth Anniversary, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 10 October 1967. (Box 18)
    - Dedication of General Cargo Pier B, Newport News, Virginia, 12 October 1967. (Box 18)
    - Virginia chapter of American Institute, Virginia Society of Professional Engineers, Roanoke, Virginia, 13 October 1967. (Box 18)
    - Democratic Campaign Rally, Abingdon, Virginia, 14 October 1967. (Box 18)
    - Wise County Rally, Fairgrounds, Wise, Virginia, 14 October 1967. (Box 18)
    - Highway Conference, Lexington, Virginia, 26 October 1967. (Box 18)
    - Political Rally, Harrisonburg, Virginia, 26 October 1967. (Box 18)
    - Ferrum Junior College, Ferrum, Virginia, 27 October 1967. (Box 18)
    - Hollins College, Hollins, Virginia, 27 October 1967. (Box 18)
    - Dedication of Main Campus Building, Northern Virginia Community college, Annandale, Virginia, 30 October 1967. (Box 18)
    - Dedication Northern Virginia Mental Health Institute, 30 October 1967. (Box 18)
    - Central High School, Victoria, Virginia, 1 November 1967. (Box 18)
    - Virginia Education Association, The Arena, 2 November 1967. (Box 18)
    - Democratic Rally, Staunton, Virginia, 3 November 1967. (Box 18)
    - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, Marion, Virginia, 4 November 1967. (Box 18)
    - Dedication of Lebanon General Hospital, Lebanon, Virginia, 5 November 1967. (Box 18)
    - English Speaking Union, The Homestead, Hot Springs, Virginia, 6 November 1967. (Box 18)
    - Westinghouse Groundbreaking, South Boston, Virginia, 9 November 1967. (Box 18)
    - Virginia Foundation for Independent Colleges, Commonwealth Club, Richmond, Virginia, 10 November 1967. (Box 18)
    - Gridiron Dinner, Williamsburg, Virginia, 11 November 1967. (Box 18)
    - Travel Writers Luncheon, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York, New York, 17 November 1967. (Box 18)
    - Report to Top Management Luncheon, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York, New York, 18 November 1967. (Box 18)
    - Dedication of New Wing, Norfolk Museum of Arts and Sciences, Norfolk, Virginia, 29 November 1967. (Box 18)
    - Dedication of Virginia Beach-Norfolk Expressway, Norfolk, Virginia, 1 December 1967. (Box 18)
    - Ingersoll-Rand Plant Luncheon, Hotel Roanoke, Roanoke, Virginia, 5 December 1967. (Box 18)
    - Eighty-fifth Anniversary, Hotel Roanoke, Roanoke, Virginia, 5 December 1967. (Box 18)
    - Testimonial Dinner for Colonel Charles W. Woodson, Jr., John Marshall Hotel, 8 December 1967. (Box 18)
    - 225th Anniversary of Louisa County, 13 December 1967. (Box 18)
    - Governor's Christmas Message, 18 December 1967. (Box 18)
    - Colon Club Breakfast, Hotel William Byrd, 20 December 1967. (Box 18)
  - Speeches, 1968., 80 items. (Box 18)
    - Budget Preview, 6 January 1968. (Box 18)
    - Address to the General Assembly, 10 January 1968. (Box 18)
    - Dedication, Virginia National Bank Building, Norfolk, Virginia, 20 January 1968. (Box 18)
    - Norfolk International Ports, Norfolk, Virginia, 20 January 1968. (Box 18)
    - School and Local Governmental Officials Banquet, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 21 January 1968. (Box 18)
    - Ruritan National Convention, Virginia Beach, Virginia, 28 January 1968. (Box 18)
    - Commemorative Session of the General Assembly, Capitol Building, Williamsburg, Virginia, 3 February 1968. (Box 18)
    - Governor's Prayer Breakfast, Hotel John Marshall, 7 February 1968. (Box 18)
    - R. J. Reynolds-Patrick County Memorial Hospital Addition, Stuart, Virginia, 11 February 1968. (Box 18)
    - Grand Master's Banquet, John Marshall Hotel, 13 February 1968. (Box 18)
    - Partners of the Alliance Dinner, Hotel John Marshall, 16 February 1968. (Box 18)
    - Introduction of Governor Carl E. Sanders, Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, 24 February 1968. (Box 18)
    - Governor's Message to General Assembly, 9 March 1968. (Box 18)
    - Tobacco Industry Exposition, Clarksville, Virginia, 20 March 1968. (Box 18)
    - Eastern Virginia Churchmen's Fellowship Dinner, Bethlehem, Virginia, 24 March 1968. (Box 18)
    - Conference on Future Patterns of Health Care, Williamsburg, Virginia, 25 March 1968. (Box 18)
    - Introduction of the Honorable Hubert H. Humphrey, Young Democratic Clubs of Virginia, 30 March 1968. (Box 18)
    - Tri-County Rotary Meeting, Suffolk, Virginia, 4 April 1968. (Box 18)
    - Division of School Superintendents, Roanoke Hotel, Roanoke, Virginia, 10 April 1968. (Box 18)
    - NIS Plant Dedication, Kenbridge, Virginia, 13 April 1968. (Box 18)
    - Order of First Families, Mayflower Hotel, Washington, 13 April 1968. (Box 18)
    - Wakefield Shad Planking, Wakefield Ruritan Club, 17 April 1968. (Box 18)
    - Virginia Association for Mental Health, The Sheraton, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 18 April 1968. (Box 18)
    - City of Hampton Recognition Banquet, Centennial Celebration of Hampton Institute, 25 April 1968. (Box 18)
    - Pilgrimage to Cape Henry, 28 April 1968. (Box 18)
    - Annual Congressional Dinner, Marriott Twin Bridges Motel, Arlington, Virginia, 29 April 1968. (Box 18)
    - Civic Center, Law Day, Norfolk, Virginia, 1 May 1968. (Box 18)
    - Appomattox River Basin Dedication, 3 May 1968. (Box 18)
    - State Agency Luncheon, John Marshall Hotel, 6 May 1968. (Box 18)
    - Virginia Association for Retarded Children Annual Conference, Jefferson Hotel, Richmond, Virginia, 11 May 1968. (Box 18)
    - Dedication of New Plant, The Newport News Daily Press, Inc., Newport News, Virginia, 11 May 1968. (Box 18)
    - Dedication, Continuing Education Center, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Blacksburg, Virginia, 13 May 1968. (Box 18)
    - Dedication of Rhoads Hall, Richmond Professional Institute, Richmond, Virginia, 14 May 1968. (Box 18)
    - First Virginia Bankshares Corporation, Marriott Twin Bridges Motor Hotel, Arlington, Virginia, 17 May 1968. (Box 18)
    - Virginia Jaycees Awards Luncheon, John Marshall, 18 May 1968. (Box 18)
    - Dedication of First National Bank, 20 May 1968. (Box 18)
    - Dedication, WRVA Studios, Richmond, Virginia, 29 May 1968. (Box 18)
    - Prelude to Independence, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1 June 1968. (Box 18)
    - Madison College Commencement, 2 June 1968. (Box 18)
    - Dedication of Holly Farms Poultry Plant, Temperanceville, Virginia, 7 June 1968. (Box 18)
    - University of Virginia Commencement Charlottesville, Virginia, 9 June 1968. (Box 18)
    - Southern Regional Educational Board, Atlanta, Georgia, 12 June 1968. (Box 18)
    - Dedication of Route 64 Interchange, 13 June 1968. (Box 18)
    - Virginia Bankers Association, Hot Springs, Virginia, 22 June 1968. (Box 18)
    - National Conference for Lieutenant Governors, Newport, Rhode Island, 28 June 1968. (Box 18)
    - Democratic State Convention, Keynote Address, Sale, Virginia, 27 July 1968. (Box 18)
    - Westinghouse Plant Announcement, Abingdon, Virginia, 29 July 1968. (Box 18)
    - Joint Ladies Night Meeting of the Civic Clubs of Pulaski County, Montgomery County and the City of Radford, Radford College, Radford, Virginia, 29 July 1968. (Box 18)
    - The Honourable the Right Worshipful Gilbert A. Cooper, C.B.E., Mayor of Hamilton, Bermuda, Jamestown, Virginia, 30 July 1968. (Box 18)
    - Commonwealth's Attorneys' Association, 3 August 1968. (Box 18)
    - Blacksburg, Virginia, American Institution of Cooperation, 5 August 1968. (Box 18)
    - Dedication of Interstate 81, Staunton, Virginia, 24 August 1968. (Box 18)
    - Peninsula Mental Health Center, Riverside Hospital, Newport News, Virginia, 8 September 1968. (Box 18)
    - National Agricultural Chemicals Association, The Greenbrier, 23 September 1968. (Box 18)
    - Dedication of Francis Scott Key Elementary School, Arlington, Virginia, 26 September 1968. (Box 18)
    - Inauguration of Luther W. White, III, Randolph-Macon College, Ashland, Virginia, 28 September 1968. (Box 18)
    - The Junior League of Richmond, Virginia, Inc., First Presbyterian Church, 4 October 1968. (Box 18)
    - State Board of Community Colleges, Williamsburg, Virginia, 4 October 1968. (Box 18)
    - Dedication of Thomas Nelson Community College, Hampton, Virginia, 4 October 1968. (Box 18)
    - Dedication of Military Science Building Virginia Military Institute, Lexington, Virginia, 5 October 1968. (Box 18)
    - Portsmouth Marine Terminal, 7 October 1968. (Box 18)
    - Falls Church Community Center Dedication, 19 October 1968. (Box 18)
    - International Business Machines Corporation, Press Briefing, Manassas, Virginia, 25 October 1968. (Box 18)
    - International Business Machines Corporation Plant Announcement Breakfast, National Guard Armory, Manassas, Virginia, 25 October 1968. (Box 18)
    - Nelson County Chamber of Commerce Dinner, Lovingston, Virginia, 26 October 1968. (Box 18)
    - TV Tape on Bond Issue, 29 October 1968. (Box 18)
    - Dedication of Dow-Badische Plant, State Capitol, 30 October 1968. (Box 18)
    - Inauguration of Dr. Fred Rogers Stair, Jr., Union Theological Seminary, Richmond, Virginia, 9 November 1968. (Box 18)
    - 50th Anniversary of the Armistice Celebration of Woodrow Wilson Birthplace Foundation, Staunton, Virginia, 11 November 1968. (Box 18)
    - State Convention of Virginia Congress of Parents and Teachers, Hotel John Marshall, 11 November 1968. (Box 18)
    - Report to Top Management Luncheon, Plaza Hotel, New York, New York, 13 November 1968. (Box 18)
    - Dedication of the Richmond Technical Center, 2020 Westwood Avenue, Richmond, Virginia, 20 November 1968. (Box 18)
    - Blue Cross-Blue Shield Building Dedication, 2015 Staples Mill Road, Richmond, Virginia, 21 November 1968. (Box 18)
    - Inauguration of Dr. Henry I. Willett, Jr., Longwood College, Farmville, Virginia, 22 November 1968. (Box 18)
    - Executive Committee, National Governors' Conference, San Francisco, California, 3 December 1968. (Box 18)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, John Marshall Hotel, Richmond, Virginia, 11 December 1968. (Box 18)
    - National Sales Convention, Watergate Hotel, Washington, D. C., 16 December 1968. (Box 18)
    - Assembly of Local Government Officials, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 17 December 1968. (Box 18)
    - Presentation of "E" Award for Export Expansion by U. S. Department of Commerce to the Island Creek Coal Company, 18 December 1968. (Box 18)
    - Tree Lighting Ceremony, State Capitol, December 1968. (Box 18)
  - Speeches, 1969., 103 items. (Box 18-19)
    - Report of Commission on Constitutional Revision, Williamsburg, Virginia, 11 January 1969. (Box 18)
    - Armed Forces Staff College Graduation, Norfolk, Virginia, 17 January 1969. (Box 18)
    - Introduction of Dr. Edgar F. Shannon, Jr., Newcomen Society Dinner, Hotel Pierre, New York, New York, 23 January 1969. (Box 18)
    - Tidewater Association of Home Builders, Lake Wright Motor Hotel, Norfolk, Virginia, 28 January 1969. (Box 18)
    - Masonic Grand Lodge of Virginia, Hotel John Marshall, 11 February 1969. (Box 18)
    - Peninsula Industrial Committee Dinner, Chamberlin Hotel, Fortress Monroe, Virginia, 14 February 1969. (Box 18)
    - Virginia Jaycees Luncheon, Roanoke, Virginia, 15 February 1969. (Box 18)
    - United Virginia Bankshares, State Planters, Richmond, Virginia, 19 February 1969. (Box 18)
    - George Washington Convocation, George Wythe High School, Richmond, Virginia, 21 February 1969. (Box 18)
    - Westinghouse Dedication, South Boston, Virginia, 22 February 1969. (Box 18)
    - Introduction of Governor Terry Sanford, Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, 22 February 1969. (Box 18)
    - Address to the General Assembly Extra Session, 26 February 1969. (Box 18)
    - Chamber of Commerce Seminar on Virginia Government, State Capitol, 3 March 1969. (Box 18)
    - Richmond Chamber of Commerce, Hotel John Marshall, 26 March 1969. (Box 18)
    - Inauguration of Dr. Martin Shotzberger, Catawba College, Salisbury, North Carolina, 28 March 1969. (Box 18)
    - Louise Obici Memorial Hospital Annual Clinical Conference with The Virginia Society of Obstetrics and Gynecology, Suffolk, Virginia, 2 April 1969. (Box 18)
    - Roanoke College Convocation, Salem, Virginia, 14 April 1969. (Box 18)
    - Association of American Universities, Williamsburg, Virginia, 16 April 1969. (Box 18)
    - John Cook Wyllie Library Dedication, Clinch Valley College, 22 April 1969. (Box 18)
    - State Highway Safety Advisory Committee, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 23 April 1969. (Box 18)
    - City of Norfolk Dinner, 26 April 1969. (Box 18)
    - Virginia Public Health Conference, Hotel Roanoke, Roanoke, Virginia, 30 April 1969. (Box 18)
    - Dedication of the Richard N. Anderson Vocational Training Building, Woodrow Wilson Rehabilitation Center, Fishersville, Virginia, 30 April 1969. (Box 18)
    - Agency Head Luncheon, 5 May 1969. (Box 19)
    - 350th Anniversary of the First General Assembly, Jamestown, Virginia, 11 May 1969. (Box 19)
    - Opening of Joint Virginia Foreign Trade Office, Brussels, Belgium, 14 May 1969. (Box 19)
    - Protocol Dinner, Brussels-Hilton Hotel, 14 May 1969. (Box 19)
    - Advisory Board on Industrial Development Luncheon, London, England, 19 May 1969. (Box 19)
    - Virginia State Ports Authority American Belgium Association Luncheon, Antwerp, Belgium, 20 May 1969. (Box 19)
    - Advisory Board on Industrial Development Luncheon Cologne, West Germany, 21 May 1969. (Box 19)
    - 350th Anniversary of Isle of Wight County, 24 May 1969. (Box 19)
    - Dinner honoring Dr. H. I. Willett, 26 May 1969. (Box 19)
    - Richard Bland College Commencement, 28 May 1969. (Box 19)
    - Virginia Beach Industrial Development Council, 29 May 1969. (Box 19)
    - Prelude to Independence, Williamsburg, Virginia, 31 May 1969. (Box 19)
    - Stratford College Graduation, Danville, Virginia, 1 June 1969. (Box 19)
    - Northern Virginia Community College Library Dedication, 3 June 1969. (Box 19)
    - Report Luncheon, Commission of the Industry of Agriculture, Hotel John Marshall, 4 June 1969. (Box 19)
    - Elkton High School Commencement, 9 June 1969. (Box 19)
    - 1969 SREB Annual Meeting, American Hotel, Miami Beach, Florida, 12 June 1969. (Box 19)
    - The Richmond Workshop for the Blind, 20 June 1969. (Box 19)
    - Virginia Treasurers' Banquet, John Marshall Hotel, 20 June 1969. (Box 19)
    - Virginia District Exchange Clubs, Norfolk, Virginia, 21 June 1969. (Box 19)
    - Charles City County Celebration, Berkeley Plantation, 4 July 1969. (Box 19)
    - SREB's 18th Legislative Work Conference, Hot Springs, Arkansas, 10 July 1969. (Box 19)
    - Norton Area Diamond Jubilee, Norton, Virginia, 12 July 1969. (Box 19)
    - Vinson Hall Dedication, McLean, Virginia, 17 July 1969. (Box 19)
    - George Mason College, Fairfax, Virginia, 18 July 1969. (Box 19)
    - Virginia Night, National Press Club, 18 July 1969. (Box 19)
    - State Fire Chiefs Banquet, Danville, Virginia, 19 July 1969. (Box 19)
    - Memorial Foundation of the Germanna colonies of Virginia, Inc., Culpeper, Virginia, 20 July 1969. (Box 19)
    - Southeastern Aviation Trade Association, Ingleside Hotel-Motel, Staunton, Virginia, 24 July 1969. (Box 19)
    - Kenrose Plant Dedication, Saltville, Virginia, 26 July 1969. (Box 19)
    - Dedication of the Richmond Area Office Building, Virginia Employment Commission, Richmond, 30 July 1969. (Box 19)
    - Introduction of The Right Honourable Dr. Horace King, Jamestown, Virginia, 2 August 1969. (Box 19)
    - Dedication of Tangier Island Airport, 7 August 1969. (Box 19)
    - 33rd National Extension, Homemakers Council Meeting, Virginia Polytechnic Institute Coliseum, Blacksburg, 12 August 1969. (Box 19)
    - Dedication of Safeway International, Richmond, 27 August 1969. (Box 19)
    - Virginia Council on State Legislation, John Marshall Hotel, Richmond, 10 September 1969. (Box 19)
    - Dedication of Ingersoll-Rand Company Plant, Roanoke County, 11 September 1969. (Box 19)
    - Introduction of the Governor of Bermuda, Jamestown Island, 14 September 1969. (Box 19)
    - Southern Governors' Conference, Opening Business Session, 15 September 1969. (Box 19)
    - Southern Governors' Conference, Introduction of Dr. Clark Kerr, Opening Business Session, 15 September 1969. (Box 19)
    - Southern Governors' Conference, Introduction of Dr. Peter P. Muirhead, Opening Business Session, 15 September 1969. (Box 19)